Wilton Historical Society Manuscript Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
- 2. Diaries and journals
  - Hallock, Charles F., 1861; This is a diary of reminiscences of his life as a soldier during the Civil War. See also PHO 410. (Box shelves, Item 30)
  - Harper, Miss, 1874; This is a diary of daily happenings while abroad. (Box shelves, Item 19)
  - Hurlbutt, David S., 1855-1856; This is a journal, mostly containing financial records and and inspirational writings. (Box shelves, Item 47)
  - Jones, Charles, 1842-1846; This letter diary contains correspondence with family and friends while in school in New Haven. (Box shelves, Item 8)
  - Merwin, Rev. Samuel John Mills, 1873-1876; This is a diary of daily happenings. (Box shelves, Item 50)
  - Middlebrook, George, 1908; This is an address and autograph book. (Box shelves, Item 46)
  - Middlebrook, Sarah Lockwood, 1888-1889; This is a diary of daily happenings, written under the name “Little Beast.” (Box shelves, Item 40)
  - Middlebrook, Sarah Lockwood, 1888; This diary covers April through December. (Box shelves, Item 39)
  - Ogden, F. Clerc, 1940; This is a journal of trip to Florida. (Box shelves, Item 5)
  - Ogden, F. Clerc, undated; This diary is entitled "Odds & Ends." It includes some notes copied from the papers of Rev. Francis Joseph Clerc, son of Laurent Clerc. (Box shelves, Item 3)
  - Ogden, F. Clerc, 1959-1960; This is a diary of daily happenings. (Box shelves, Item 35)
  - Ogden, William, 1830; This is a journal of private musings written while living in Texas. It is titled by the author as his "Fragment Book." (Box shelves, Item 49)
  - Rockwell, Lewis, undated; This is an address book for Lewis Rockwell's business in furniture repair. (Box shelves, Item 48)
  - Rundle and Weston Tea Room, 1908; This is the guest book of a tea room run by Abby Rundle and Ethel Betts Weston (Mrs. George) at 250 Danbury Road (J. P. Fitch House). It contains the names of many local and nearby residents. (Box shelves, Item 6)
  - School District #7, 1866-1906; This diary contains minutes of meetings. See also Book 372.97469. (Box shelves, Item 38)
  - Scott, Handford, 1851; This is a pocket diary covering February through May. (Box shelves, Item 34)
  - Scott, Hanford, 1871-1877; This is a diary and daybook. It also contains correspondence from S. E. Olmsted (1877) and a paper on an agricultural insurance company. (Box shelves, Item 21)
  - Shepherd, Lewis, 1852-1853; This is a diary of daily happenings and accounts. (Box shelves, Item 20)
  - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1881-1889; This diary is labelled "Nellie's Diary." (Box shelves, Item 1)
  - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1915-1917; This is a diary of daily happenings. (Box shelves, Item 10, 11)
  - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1955; This is a diary of a trip to Great Britain. (Box shelves, Item 12)
  - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1914; This is a diary of a trip to Great Britain. (Box shelves, Item 13)
  - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1916; This is a diary titled "Gypsing." It covers a five-day journey from Cannondale to Kent and back home. (Box shelves, Item 33)
  - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Fitch, 1917-1918; This is a diary of village life and activities. (Box shelves, Item 75)
  - Wittwell, Leslie, 1918-1919; This is a diary from World War One. (Box shelves, Item 32)
- 3. People and families
  - Marvin family - Estate records and legal documents, undated; Contents donated by Deborah Weinstein. (Box 571, Folder 571)
  - Abbott family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 80)
  - Adams family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 85)
  - Adams, Charles Nathan - Papers, undated; See also Diaries, C. N. Adams. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 100)
  - Allee family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 105)
  - Allen, Devere - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 106)
  - Ambler family - Correspondence, 1925-1941; Includes correspondence with the Daughters of the American Revolution, letters from Elizabeth Ambler to her family, and other miscellaneous correspondence. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 107, 112, 113)
  - Ambler family - Legal documents, 1964-1973 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 110, 111)
  - Ambler family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 108)
  - Ambler family - Papers, 1881-1938; Contains manuscripts including "The Democrat," "New England Homestead," "Busy Day at Lake Placid, NY," and Elizabeth Raymond Ambler Graduation Certificate from Roberts-Brarh School. (Box Cabinet: 24, Folder MC 7-10)
  - Ambler family - School records, 1938; Includes school yearbooks. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 114)
  - Ambler, Charles M. - School records, 1889-1890; Includes Charles M. Ambler's school essays. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 109)
  - Arnold family - Papers, 1767-1941; Includes documentation on births, deaths, and marriages. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 120)
  - Ayres, Sarah - Estate records, 1832 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 122)
  - Beardsley, Jeanette and Sigourney Van Zandt - Literary works, 1857 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 530)
  - Bedient family - Correspondence, 1901-1936 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 124b)
  - Bedient family - Genealogical correspondence, undated; Includes correspondence on genealogy. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 128, 129, 130)
  - Bedient, Art - Papers, 1950-1952 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 123)
  - Bedient, Charles - Estate records, 1884 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 124a)
  - Bedient, David - Papers, 1860-1865 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 125)
  - Bedient, Frederick - Papers, 1889 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 126)
  - Bedient, Harvey and Leona Bedient-Cronchley - Papers, 1929-1959 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 127)
  - Belden, Azor - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 135)
  - Belden, Daniel - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 137)
  - Belden, David - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 139)
  - Belden, Elizabeth - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 141)
  - Belden, George - Papers, 1827 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 143)
  - Belden, John - Papers, 1739 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 145)
  - Belden, Martha - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 147)
  - Belden, Mary - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 149)
  - Belden, Nathan M. - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 151, 153)
  - Belden, Reuben B. - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 155a)
  - Belden, Rev. David - Correspondence, 1789-1792 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 140)
  - Belden, Richard - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 155b)
  - Belden, Robert - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 156)
  - Belden, Samuel - Papers, 1769-1822 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 157)
  - Belden, Thomas - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 159)
  - Belden, William - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 161)
  - Benedict family - Papers, 1864-1867 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 165)
  - Bennett family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 166b)
  - Bennett, Frank R. - Correspondence, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 166a)
  - Berry, Capt. C. C. Berry - Certificates, 1843-1853; Includes framed certificates. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 167)
  - Bethel family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 168)
  - Betts family - Papers, undated; See also MAN, Betts-Raymond store papers. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 170a)
  - Betts, Allen H. - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 170b)
  - Betts, Andrews - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 172)
  - Betts, Asahel R. - Papers, 1817 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 171)
  - Betts, Burwel - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 173a)
  - Betts, Capt. Daniel - Financial records, 1794-1796 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 176)
  - Betts, Carmi - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 173b)
  - Betts, Charles - Correspondence, 1843; Includes letter to Ebenezer and Polly Church. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 174)
  - Betts, Daniel Jr. - Legal correspondence, 1808; Includes a court summons for unpaid debt. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 175)
  - Betts, Elijah - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 177a)
  - Betts, Ira - Papers, 1810-1826 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 177ab)
  - Betts, James - Property records, 1720-1730; Includes information on land purchases. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 177b)
  - Betts, Lewis - Papers, 1795-1815 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 178)
  - Betts, Samuel - Correspondence, 1803-1804 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 180)
  - Betts, Stephen - Papers, 1829 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 181)
  - Birchard family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 183b)
  - Birchard, Edwin - Financial records, 1840 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 200)
  - Birchard, Eli - Financial and estate records, 1811-1856; Includes receipts. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 183a, 205)
  - Blackmar, Dana - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 184)
  - Bouton, Lewis - Financial records, 1831; Includes receipts, which suggest that Lewis Bouton was a shoemaker. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 185)
  - Brown, Benjamin - Papers, 1874 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 192)
  - Browne, Bradley - Correspondence, 1884 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 195)
  - Campbell, James - Legal documents, 1783; Includes a power of attorney to Nicholson. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 220)
  - Cannon, Charles - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 225)
  - Chandler family - Papers, 1827-1913; Includes information on births, deaths, and marriages. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 250)
  - Chichester, Aaron - Papers, 1815-1860 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 253)
  - Chichester, Abraham - Papers, 1780-1820 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 254a)
  - Chichester, Dr. Abraham - Papers, 1785-1800; Includes Dr. Abraham's list of patients. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 252)
  - Chichester, Henry - Papers, undated; Includes Town Clerk Henry Chichester's papers and scrapbook pages. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 255, 256)
  - Chichester, Polly - Legal documents, undated; Includes Polly Chichester's will. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 254c)
  - Clerc, Laurent - Asylum papers, 1822-1833; Ogden family. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 674)
  - Clerc, Laurent - Miscellaneous papers, 1785-1869; Ogden family. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 676)
  - Clerc, Laurent - Portraits, 1822; Ogden family. The portraits are by C. W. Peale. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 678)
  - Clerc, Laurent - Travel to England and France, 1846; Ogden family. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 680)
  - Clerc, Rev. Francis - Estate records, undated; Ogden family. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 673)
  - Clerc, Rev. Francis - Literary works, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 535)
  - Clerc, Rev. Francis - Papers, 1835-1907; Ogden family. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 672)
  - Comstock family - Papers, undated; Includes a fragment of a diary. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 259, 260)
  - Comstock, Benajah Strong - Estate records, 1815; Includes estate inventory and distribution records. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 261)
  - Comstock, Charles - Correspondence, 1852; Includes a letter from Theo Dilavergne. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 262)
  - Comstock, James - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 263)
  - Comstock, John - Estate administration records, 1839-1857; Includes John Comstock's papers as administrator of the estate of Hannah Middlebrook. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 264)
  - Comstock, Matthias - Estate records, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 265b)
  - Comstock, Matthias - Property records, 1826-1835 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 265a)
  - Comstock, Nathan - Financial records, 1852-1867; Includes a receipt for Wilton Railroad Depot Construction, and miscellaneous other receipts. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 266)
  - Comstock, Samuel - Correspondence, legal documents, and property records, undated; Includes Bond with Mead and a Land Survey. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 268)
  - Comstock, Strong - Correspondence, undated; Includes a letter from Strong Comstock's mother. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 270)
  - Darling, Sarah - Papers, 1851; Includes information on Sarah Darling's appointment as overseer. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 275)
  - Davenport, George - Papers, 1793-1913 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 280)
  - Davenport, Nathan - Papers, 1818 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 290)
  - Davenport, Sarah - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 292)
  - Davis, James - Estate records, 1787-1833 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 293a)
  - Davis, Lewis - Estate records, 1833 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 293b)
  - Davis, Lewis v. Rufus Olmstead - Lawsuit, 1833-1841 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 293c)
  - DeForest family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 295)
  - Dewing family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 296)
  - DeWitt, Seymour - School records, 1886; Includes his Rhinebeck Academy Diploma. (Box Cabinet: 24, Folder MC 7-12)
  - Douglas, Damon - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 297a, 297b, 297c, 297d)
  - Fillow family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 299aa)
  - Fisher, Bessie - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 299b)
  - Fitch family - Homestead, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 322)
  - Fitch family - Papers, undated; Includes Fitch family ephemera. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 309)
  - Fitch, Agnes - Correspondence, 1885 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 301)
  - Fitch, Agnes - Wedding, 1886 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 300)
  - Fitch, Ann - Financial records, 1822 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 302)
  - Fitch, Arthur - Correspondence, 1876-1915; Includes letters to Arthur Fitch's sisters in Wilton, England in the 1870s and 1880s, and to his son Peter in 1915. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 303, 304)
  - Fitch, Arthur - Drawings, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 305)
  - Fitch, Edward Sherman - Correspondence, 1894; Includes a letter to Edward Sherman Fitch's mother. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 306)
  - Fitch, Frances "Fannie" - Dance and musical performances, 1877-1891 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 310)
  - Fitch, Frances "Fannie" - Scrapbook, 1886-1917; This is a copy. See Scrapbooks for original. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 312)
  - Fitch, Frances "Fannie" - Wedding, 1889 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 311)
  - Fitch, Gov. Thomas - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 340)
  - Fitch, Harriet "Hattie" - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 313)
  - Fitch, Isaac - Correspondence, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 323)
  - Fitch, Joseph - Estate records, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 326)
  - Fitch, Joseph - Papers, undated; Includes information on Joseph Fitch's commission as postmaster. See also MC 7-2. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 325)
  - Fitch, Maud L. - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 330)
  - Fitch, Richard - Property records, undated; Includes papers on Dick's Inn agreement with railroad, and an attempt to relocate railroad station to homestead. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 332, 333)
  - Fitch, Rosemary - Correspondence, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 334a)
  - Fitch, Sarah - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 334b)
  - Fitch, Sherman - Correspondence, 1885-1889; Sherman Fitch was a Notary Public. This file includes a letter to Jeanette Lyall and other miscellaneous material. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 335)
  - Fitch, Sherman - Correspondence and financial records, undated; Includes papers on Thanksgiving and correspondence. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 338)
  - Fitch, Sherman - Estate records, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 339)
  - Fitch, Sherman - Wedding, undated; Includes a copy of Sherman Fitch's marriage proposal to Sarah Jones. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 336)
  - Fitch-Sturges family - Genealogic chart, undated (Box Cabinet: 24, Folder MC 7-8)
  - Fitch-Sturges, Helen Elizabeth "Nellie" - Correspondence, undated; Includes correspondence with Mabel and Helen Elizabeth Sturges (her daughters), and other correspondence. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 315, 316)
  - Fitch-Sturges, Helen Elizabeth "Nellie" - Diary and newspaper clippings, undated; Includes other miscellaneous material. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 317)
  - Fitch-Sturges, Helen Elizabeth "Nellie" - Wedding, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 314)
  - Gaylord, William - Estate records, 1767 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 345)
  - Gilbert, Eben - Legal documents, 1908; Includes a mechanic's lien. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 347)
  - Gilbert, Eli - Papers, 1840s; Eli Gilbert was a merchant. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 348)
  - Gilbert, George B. - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 350, 351)
  - Godfrey family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 355)
  - Gorham, John - Legal documents, 1890; Includes a quit claim deed. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 357a)
  - Gregory family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 357b)
  - Gregory family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 370c)
  - Gregory, Abby - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 358a)
  - Gregory, Charles - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 359)
  - Gregory, Ebenezer - Legal documents, 1805; Includes Ebenezer Gregory's will. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 360)
  - Gregory, Ezra - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 362)
  - Gregory, Giles - Papers, 1827-1854 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 365)
  - Gregory, Harriet (Clark) - Correspondence, undated; Includes a letter to her sister Sarah, written before 1831. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 366)
  - Gregory, Helen - Correspondence, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 368)
  - Gregory, Helen - Legal documents, undated; Includes abstracts of wills. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 369a)
  - Gregory, Helen - Notes, undated; Includes information on Gregory neighbors and land on Belden Hill. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 369b)
  - Gregory, Helen - Property records, undated-1891; Includes notes and deed research, and abstract of Title of Property on Belden Hill (Gregory / Hickok / Gilbert) dating to 1891. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 367, 369e)
  - Gregory, Helen - Research on Gregory family history, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 369d)
  - Gregory, Helen - Research on Gregory family names, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 369c)
  - Gregory, James - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 364)
  - Gregory, Jehiel - Estate records, 1823 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 369f)
  - Gregory, John - Legal documents, 1870; Includes a release of lien from R. Ralston. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 370a)
  - Gregory, Matthew - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 370b)
  - Gregory, Moses - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 371)
  - Gregory, Stewart - Papers, 1879 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 372)
  - Gregory, William - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 376)
  - Grumman family - Papers, undated; See also MC 7-3. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 380)
  - Grumman, Edwin - Financial records, 1869-1924 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 382)
  - Grumman, Emilia Betts - School records, 1850; Includes school records. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 384)
  - Grumman, LeGrand - Correspondence, 1867-1895; Includes letters from L. L. and G. M. Allen. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 386)
  - Grumman, Seth - Carriage purchase, 1907 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 392)
  - Grumman, Seth - Estate administration records, 1879-1880; Includes his papers as administrator of estate of William Beers. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 390)
  - Grumman, Seth - Estate administration records, 1874-1879; Includes Seth Grumman's papers as administrator of estates of Elisa Grumman and Jehiel Grumman. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 408, 410, 412)
  - Grumman, Seth - Financial records, 1800-1908; Includes receipts for grain and fertilizer purchased from 1889-1908. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 388, 402, 404)
  - Grumman, Seth - Insurance, 1869-1875 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 396)
  - Grumman, Seth - Legal documents, 1876-1877 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 398)
  - Grumman, Seth - Papers, 1876-1908; Includes miscellaneous papers. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 400)
  - Grumman, Seth - Papers on Gilbert and Bennett, 1883-1888 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 394)
  - Grumman, Seth - Tax records, 1863-1877 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 406)
  - Hallock, Charles F. - Military records, 1861-1864; Charles F. Hallock was a Civil War soldier. File includes his papers and Confederate money. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 413)
  - Handricks, Daniel - Papers, 1863; Includes a certificate. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 414)
  - Hanford, Bartlett - Estate records, 1839 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 415a)
  - Hanford, Betsey - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 415b)
  - Hanford, Hannah - Estate records, 1843-1845 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 416)
  - Hanford, Joseph - Estate records, 1844 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 417a)
  - Hawley, Ezehial - Estate records, 1790 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 417aa)
  - Hedburg family - Property records, 1880-1902; Includes a property title. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 417ab)
  - Hill, Calvin - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 417b)
  - Homan, Corp. William Henry - Correspondence, diary, and military records, 1860-1862; Includes correspondence and a diary relating to the Civil War. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 1156)
  - Hoyt family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 417c)
  - Hoyt, Jotham - Property records, 1825-1841; Includes copies of deeds. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 418a)
  - Hoyt, Samuel - Legal documents, 1818; Includes a power of attorney. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 418b)
  - Hoyt, Solomon - Estate records, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 419a)
  - Hoyt, Thaddeus - Estate records, 1847; Includes papers on the estate auction. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 419b)
  - Hubbell, W. K. J. - Military records, 1918-1919; Includes items relating to World War One. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 478)
  - Hurlbutt family - Papers, 1831-1944 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 479)
  - Hurlbutt, David - Legal documents, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 480b)
  - Hurlbutt, David - Papers, 1823 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 480a)
  - Hurlbutt, E. A. - Diary and financial records, undated; Includes a ledger. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 485b)
  - Hurlbutt, J. Belden - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 481)
  - Hurlbutt, John - Papers, 1850 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 482a)
  - Hurlbutt, Josephine - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 482b)
  - Hurlbutt, Lewis - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 483a)
  - Hurlbutt, Nelson - Papers, 1888-1939 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 483b)
  - Hurlbutt, William B. - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 484)
  - Hyatt, Aaron - Papers, 1817 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 485ba)
  - Ingram, Dr. H. D. - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 485bc)
  - Jackson, Clarence and Emma - Papers, undated; Includes documents relating to their fruit farm, birth certificate, property, and tax records. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 485c)
  - Jackson, Henry - Legal documents, 1686; Includes a will. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 486a)
  - Jackson, Henry - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 485ca)
  - Jackson, John - Correspondence and financial records, undated; Includes receipts and cancelled checks. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 486b)
  - Jackson, Mary - Property records, 1888; Includes a quit claim deed. See also George Gilbert. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 486c)
  - James, George - Property records, 1837; Includes a lease. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 487a, 487b)
  - Jelif, Charles - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 489)
  - Jennings, Moses - Papers, 1839; Includes a death notice. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 490)
  - Jones, Charles - Financial records, 1893-1895; Includes receipts. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 500)
  - Jones, Eugene D. - Papers, undated; Includes a speech. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 501)
  - Keeler family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 502)
  - Keeler, Abigail - Estate records, 1832-1852 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 504, 506)
  - Keeler, Chauncy - Estate records, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 508, 509, 510, 511, 512)
  - Keeler, Isaac - Estate records, 1816 (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 516)
  - Keeler, Isaac - Military records, undated; Includes information on a his military commission. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 515)
  - Keeler, Isaac - Property records, 1816; Includes a lease to Sarah Ayres. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 517)
  - Keeler, John - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 514)
  - Keeler, Naomi - Legal documents, 1809; Includes articles of agreement. (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 518)
  - Knapp family - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 518b)
  - Lambert, David - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 523)
  - Lambert, David Samuel Rogers - Murder, 1897; Includes newspaper and magazine articles. (Box Cabinet: 24, Folder MC 7-4)
  - Lambert, Eva Ogden - Papers, undated (Box Cabinet: 7, Folder 518c)